{
    "Items": [
        {
            "question": "Which vocabulary represent to 小型轎車?",
			"correctAns": "subcompact car",
			"wrongAns": ["car", "super car","touring car"]
        },
		{
			"question": "Which vocabulary represent to 觀光汽車?",
			"correctAns": "sightseeing car ",
			"wrongAns": ["tour car ", "tour bus", "looking car"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Which vocabulary represent to 微型轎車?",
			"correctAns": "baby car",
			"wrongAns": ["small car", "micro car ", "road car "]
		},
		{
			"question": "Which vocabulary represent to 拖車?",
			"correctAns": "tow truck",
			"wrongAns": ["tow train", "tow bus", "pull car" ]
		},
		{
			"question": "Which vocabulary represent to 多用途車?",
			"correctAns": "general purpose car",
			"wrongAns": ["multiple car", "functional car", "posh car", "Bus"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Which vocabulary represent to 太陽能汽車?",
			"correctAns": "Solar car",
			"wrongAns": ["Wind car", "Energy car", "sun car", "water car"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Which vocabulary represent to 改裝汽車?",
			"correctAns": "remoulded car",
			"wrongAns": ["change car", "model car", "Compact Car", "SUV"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Which vocabulary represent to 三廂轎車?",
			"correctAns": "Sedan",
			"wrongAns": ["Solo", "Solar", "Sona", "Triple-seat car"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Which vocabulary represent to 警車?",
			"correctAns": "Police car",
			"wrongAns": ["Fire car", "Ambulance", "alert car", "mail car"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Which vocabulary represent to 郵車?",
			"correctAns": "mail car",
			"wrongAns": ["package car", "office car", "racing car", "trailer"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Which vocabulary represent to 腳踏車?",
			"correctAns": "bicycle",
			"wrongAns": ["moped", "bike", "motorcycle", "racer"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Which vocabulary represent to 獨木舟?",
			"correctAns": "canoe",
			"wrongAns": ["ferry", "sailboat", "boat", "merchant ship"]
		}
    ]
}